https://www.farmercoop.com/privacy-policy

Farmers Coop Fort Smith, AR
Farmers Coop Mena, AR (Southwest Outdoor Center)
Contact Us
Home | Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy set by Farmer’s Co-op
On our site we collect the following (only after your consent):
Name
Email address
Mailing address
Phone number
We only collect this information from you when you:
Register on our site
Subscribe to a newsletter
Fill out a form
The information collected from you is used in the following ways:
To improve the website
To improve customer service
To send periodic emails
How do we protect visitor information?
We use vulnerability scanning and/or scanning to PCI standards.
We implement security measures when a user:
enters, submits, or accesses their information.
We do not use cookies for tracking purposes
Third Party Disclosure
We may transfer your non-identifiable information to third parties (for example, Google Analytics to track our site traffic). We may also transfer your identifiable information, but only to trusted third parties (for example, the software we use to email you–we will NEVER sell your information to spammers).
Third party links
We do not include or offer third party products or services on our website.
Google
We have not enable Google Adwords on our site but we may do so on the future.
California Online Privacy Protection Act
According to CalOPPA we agree to the following:
Users can visit our site anonymously
Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page, or as a minimum on the first significant page after entering our website.
Our Privacy Policy link includes the word ‘Privacy’, and can be easily be found on the page specified above.
Contact Information:
Farmer’s Co-op
Contact Us
It is the responsibility of website users to stay up to date with any privacy policy changes:
On our Privacy Policy Page
Users are able to change their personal information:
By emailing us
How does our site handle do not track signals?
We honor them and do not track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.
COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)
We do not specifically market to children under 13
We collect your email address:
To send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.
To market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to your clients after the original transaction has occurred
To be accordance with CANSPAM we agree to the following:
We will NOT use false, or misleading subjects or email addresses
We will identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way
We will include the physical address of our business or site headquarters
We will monitor third party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.
We will honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly
We will give an ‘opt-out’ or ‘unsubscribe’ option
If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can follow the instructions at the bottom of each email.
Search for:
Share this page
Events & Promotions
« Nov
Jan »
November 23:
Lincoln Secret Santa Angel Tree-Donate Today
December 7:
Christmas Tree Challenge 2020 – Vote Now!
December 24:
Holiday Hours At Farmers Coop
December 25:
Holiday Hours At Farmers Coop
December 31:
Holiday Hours At Farmers Coop
January 1:
Sign Up NowFor Email Marketing you can trust.
Search ...
Search
Want be the first to hear about sales, new arrivals, events, and Email only
specials?
Sign up for our emails and be the first to know.
Newsletter
Sign Up Now
For Email Marketing you can trust.
×
